<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MLRumble</title>
    <link>http://mlrumble.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MLRumble</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mlrumble.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://mlrumble.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mlrumble.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A blog for my Machine learning perumbulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Author</title>
      <link>http://mlrumble.github.io/author/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mlrumble.github.io/author/</guid>
      <description>A not so known Machine Learning Engineer/ Data scientist. Will rather like to blog anonymously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning By Andrew NG Course 1 review</title>
      <link>http://mlrumble.github.io/posts/deeplearning-andrew-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 10:06:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mlrumble.github.io/posts/deeplearning-andrew-1/</guid>
      <description>I recently completed the first deep learning course by Andrew Ng and I definitely am feeling enlightened. Takes me back to those early days when Andrew came up with his first machine learning course.
  Deep Learning Course Structure   About the course, Andrew has achieved mastery in explaining difficult concepts in an easy to understand way. The nomenclature he follows is different from all other tutorials and courses on the net, and I hope it catches on as it is pretty helpful in understanding all the basic concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Solr Service with Python on Mac</title>
      <link>http://mlrumble.github.io/posts/using-a-solr-service-with-python-on-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 18:06:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mlrumble.github.io/posts/using-a-solr-service-with-python-on-mac/</guid>
      <description>Started working on Solr for some search thing recently. It is difficult to find simple instructions to get it up and running. So here is my effort on the same.
1. Install Solr Server on your Laptop I am using a Mac so the simplest way I could do that is by using
# Install Solr Server brew install solr # Start Solr Server with example configuration solr -e techproducts # Install solr for Python pip install pysolr Running the command solr -e techproducts gives us this message, and a whole lot of other things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I created this Website using Hugo and used a custom domain with github pages</title>
      <link>http://mlrumble.github.io/posts/blog-created/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 18:06:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mlrumble.github.io/posts/blog-created/</guid>
      <description>Started up with blogging on Machine learning. Thought about using the Hugo static file generator. Here is code I used and the changes I made. Thought might be helpful to someone.
Deploy the Website: Go to the quickstart tutorial and follow through with the steps. The main steps are:
brew install hugo # replace with your site name hugo new site mlrumble cd mlrumble;\ git init;\ git submodule add https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>